…確定這是什麼的問題
...a matter of establishing what this is.
如果這確實是恐怖主義行為 那麼是誰造成的
If indeed this was an act of terrorism, then who caused it?
整個東海岸的所有電力都用光了
All of the electricity across the entire Eastern Seaboard is out.
人們命令呆在室內直到接到進一步的通知並且…
People ordered to stay indoors until further notice and to...
…簡直就是天啟
...is nothing short of apocalyptic.
…大都會區 除了芝加哥
...metropolitan areas, in addition to Chicago,
被完全包圍
are completely surrounded.
我們仍在等待官方公告
We're still awaiting an official announcement,
but Congress is believed to have accepted unconditionally
但是國會被認為是無條件接受的
all terms of armistice offered.
所有停戰條款
…在過去的幾個小時裏恢復了電源
...and with power restored in the last few hours,
-戒嚴…-這太花時間了
-martial law... -This is taking too long.
現在所有的美國軍隊都回到了他們的基地
Now all US military forces are returning to their bases
帶著命令轉身退後直到下一個命令…
with orders to turn in arms and stand down until further orders...
報告現在從東京 雅加達 羅馬傳播開來
Reports are spreading now from Tokyo, Jakarta, Rome.
與外部新聞來源的聯繫是零星的
Contact with outside news sources has been sporadic
由於特倫頓電網的毀滅性故障
since the devastating failure of the Trenton power grid,
但目擊者證實…
but eyewitnesses confirm...
…大多數國際政府似乎都遵守…
...that the majority of international governments appear to comply...
警官 我要往北上去
Officer, I need to get up north.
你要去哪裏 警探
Where you going, Detective?
你沒有接到命令
You not get orders?
停車 停車
Stop the car. Stop the car.
把手從方向盤上拿開
Take your hands off the wheel.
-停止發動機 -嗯…
-Stop the engine. -Um...
-哦 我的…停車
-Oh, my... -Stop the car!
…似乎追隨了美國的領導
...appear to have followed the US' lead
並且正在與第一批立法者力量進行談判
and are entering into negotiations with this first wave of Legislator forces.
聽著 我們應該給學校打電話嗎 可能有個計劃
Look, should we call the school? There may be a plan.
我不會翻身的 我們需要出去重新組合 然後反擊
I'm not rolling over! We need to get out and regroup, then fight back.
J.
J... John!
John.
轉身
Turn around.
Turn around!
快點 約翰
Come on, John.
關閉非常有序
The shutdown was very orderly.
有某種程度的合作
There's been a sort of a level of cooperation
你可以在這裏看到
that you can see here.
我愛你 魯拉
I love you, Rula.
另一個避免湖濱駕車的提醒
Another reminder to avoid Lake Shore Drive
如果你不是今晚被邀請參加團結慶典的幸運千人之一
if you're not one of the lucky thousands invited to tonight's unity celebration.
這項活動已經進行了一年多
This event has been in the works for the better part of a year,
市長李艾德將出席
with Mayor Ed Lee expected to attend.
所有的標誌都指向這個…
All signs are pointing to this...
你見過太陽落在湖的另一邊嗎
You ever see the sun set on the other side of the lake?
不 太陽從這邊落下 笨蛋 西側
No. The sun sets this side, dummy. West side.
是啊
Yeah.
我知道
I know.
我晚點來看你 好嗎
I'll come and see you later, all right?
嘿 喲
Hey, yo.
船準備好了 夥計
Boat's all ready, man,
所以你今天把它拿下來 我們就離開這裏
so you pull this off today, we're out of here.
嘿 冷靜點
Hey, cool it.
全天候盯著我看
Got eyes on me 24-7.
不 去那邊看看她
No shit. Check her out, up there.
喲 每天 那個女巫都像鐘錶一樣看著我
Yo, every day, that witch be watching me like clockwork.
嘿 我看見一隻老鼠
Hey, I see a rat.
納克
Narc!
哦
Oh...
走吧
Let's go.
-你兄弟是個傳奇 夥計 喲 快點
-Your bro's a legend, man. -Yo, come on.
你最後一次見到它是什麼時候
When's the last time you seen one?
蟑螂
A roach?
很久以前 來吧 夥計 我們走 聽著 我今天不能遲到
A long time ago. Come on, man, let's go. Look, I can't be late today.
我應該像你哥哥那樣闖進來 把整堆螞蟻都剷平
I should break in like your brother did and bulldoze that whole ant heap.
他們不能永遠躲在那裏 夥計
They can't hide down there forever, man.
我馬上就好
I'll be ready in a minute.
我時間不多
I don't have much time.
但我想見你
But I wanted to see you.
好吧 那我們最好把生意讓開
Well, then we'd better get business out of the way.
我不能這麼做
I can't do this.
我們去睡覺吧
Let's go to bed.
我們在做什麼 這是個錯誤
What are we doing? This is a mistake.
沒有錯誤 只有命運
There's no such thing as a mistake. There's only fate.
你是警察 你不會被抓住的 -對不起
-You're a cop. You won't get caught. -I'm sorry.
等待 等待
Wait. Wait.
你忘了你來這裏是為了什麼
You forgot what you came here for.
提防帶禮物的希臘人
Beware Greeks bearing gifts.
-我有一個二手身份證-老鷹降落了
-I got a secondhand ID. -So the Eagle has landed?
鳳凰 你應該注意
Phoenix. You should pay attention.
你看到了嗎 二手貨是二手貨
You got a visual? Secondhand is secondhand.
你還從下面得到授權嗎
You still got authorization from below?
他們在計劃一件大事
They're planning something big.
它們不存在
They don't exist.
我們就是這麼說外星人的
That's what we said about aliens.
真有趣
That's funny.
還記得柳條公園嗎
Remember Wicker Park?
是的 蟑螂把它們弄成了塵土 他們走了
Yeah, the roaches fucked them into dust. They're gone.
不要用那個詞
Don't use that word.
What?
什麼
Since when has this become your personal work space?
這是什麼時候開始成為你的個人工作空間的
The resistance wasn't wiped out after Wicker Park.
在柳條公園之後 抵抗運動沒有被消滅
They went to ground. I figured it out.
他們走到地上 我明白了
They're communicating through the classifieds.
他們通過分類廣告進行交流
Their network regrouped here in Pilsen, right under our noses.
他們的網絡在皮爾森重組 就在我們眼皮底下
You got nothing that shows that.
你什麼都沒有
Theses... These are memorials.
論文…這些是紀念物
Legislators got 'em all. You're searching for ghosts, Bill.
立法者把他們都抓起來了 你在找鬼 比爾
If we don't act now, we're facing a full-blown insurgency.
如果我們現在不採取行動 我們將面臨全面的叛亂
I suggest you keep that idea to yourself.
我建議你自己保留這個想法
好吧 太晚了 已經踢到樓下了
Well, too late. Already kicked it downstairs.
在專員的辦公桌上
It's on the commissioner's desk.
你為什麼這麼做
Why did you do that?
他們沒有走
They're not gone.
-你沒被跟蹤 -沒有
-You weren't followed? -No.
訓練結束了
Training's over.
你支持這個
And you back this?
我支持第一
I back Number One.
通往封閉區的路是穿過士兵陣地
The way to the Closed Zone is through Soldier Field.
隊伍今晚出發
Team goes tonight.
這是士兵場
It's Soldier Field.
團結集會
The Unity Rally?
從巴博薩得到你需要的
Get what you need from Barbosa.
士兵場離封閉區有幾英里
Soldier Field is miles from the Closed Zone.
-那是怎麼讓我們回到裏面的 -我相信你
-How's that get us back inside? -I'm trusting you.
-他會送貨的 他必須這麼做 今天就是
-He'll deliver. -He has to. Today's the day.
加布裏埃爾·德拉蒙德 上午7:04
Gabriel Drummond, 7:04 a.m.
哦 好了 就這樣……
Oh, there it goes. There it goes...
哦 結束了 這是尖叫聲
Oh, it's over. It's a squeaker.
那是一分半鐘的事
That was a matter of a minute and a half.
四處走走 從其他角度看一看
Walk around, take a look from other angles.
哦
Oh!
15分鐘
Fifteen minutes.
另一個避免湖濱駕車的提醒
Another reminder to avoid Lake Shore Drive
如果你不是今晚被邀請參加團結慶典的幸運千人之一
if you're not one of the lucky thousands invited to tonight's unity celebration.
這項活動已經進行了一年多
This event has been in the works for the better part of a year,
市長李艾德將出席
with Mayor Ed Lee expected to attend.
所有跡象都表明這是一個罕見的場合
All signs are pointing to this being one of those rare occasions
當立法者可能只是露面的時候
when the Legislators might just make an appearance.
車輛正在士兵場周圍繞行
Traffic's being routed around Soldier Field,
人們很早就出現了
and folks are showing up early.
這是多麼美好的夜晚啊
What a night here this is.
值得慶祝的事 另一個提醒…
Lots to celebrate. Another reminder...
你明白嗎
You got it or what?
…如果你不是幸運的幾千人之一
...if you're not one of the lucky thousands
應邀參加今晚的團結慶典
invited to tonight's unity celebration.
這項活動已經進行了一年多
This event has been in the works for the better part of a year,
市長李艾德將出席
with Mayor Ed Lee expected to attend.
所有跡象都表明這是一個罕見的場合
All signs are pointing to this being one of those rare occasions
當立法者可能只是露面的時候
when the Legislators might just make an appearance.
車輛正在士兵場周圍繞行
Traffic's being routed around Soldier Field,
人們很早就出現了
and folks are showing up early.
這是多麼美好的夜晚啊 值得慶祝的事
What a night here this is. Lots to celebrate.
在這裏
Here.
另一個避免湖濱駕車的提醒
Another reminder to avoid Lake Shore Drive
如果你不是幸運的千人之一…
if you're not one of the lucky thousands...
希望你能好好利用它
Hope you put it to good use.
這項活動在一年中的大部分時間都在進行中
This event has been in the works for the better part of a year.
所有跡象都表明這是一個罕見的場合
All signs are pointing to this being one of those rare occasions
當立法者可能只是露面的時候
when the Legislators might just make an appearance.
拜託
Please.
我什麼都沒做
I haven't done anything.
-我什麼都沒做 -嘿 嘿 別管她
-I haven't done anything. -Hey. Hey, leave her alone.
拜託 我們能不能…
Please, can we just...
行星外運輸…
Off-planet transport...
嘿 快點 兄弟 你得看看這個
Hey, hurry up, bro. You got to check this out.
她只需要汽油
All she needs is gas.
-該死的 喲 -對嗎
-Damn, yo. -Right?
她也很快
She's fast, too.
一定要從外面過去
Got to be to get past what's out there,
但是沒有檢查站 所以我們到了另一邊
but there's no checkpoint, so we get to the other side,
這就是自由 寶貝
and it's freedom, baby.
希望如此
Let's hope so.
那麼 你拿到煙了嗎
So, did you get the cigarette?
-我當然明白了 -媽的 那我們就離開這裏
-Of course I got it. -Shit, then we're out of here.
喲 我就要像披頭巾高手一樣來對付這些蟑螂了
Yo, I'm about to come like Scarf ace on these roaches.
呸
Bah!
我不打不倒
I'm not going down without a fight.
喲 你用什麼換來的
Yo, what did you trade for that?
直接現金 而且已經滿了
Straight cash, and it's fully loaded.
哦 我們需要的汽油錢
Oh, the cash we need for gas?
冷靜 夥計 這是一項投資
Chill, man. It's an investment.
你為什麼總是絆倒我 夥計
Why are you always trippin', man?
人們都在為我們在這裏得到的東西而渴望
People are jonesing for what we got out here!
什麼 你覺得你現在在大聯盟 尤吉斯 哈
What, you think you in the big leagues now, Jurgis, huh?
喲 那該死的東西會給我們帶來嚴重的麻煩
Yo, that shit right there will get us in some serious trouble.
我討厭這種口對口的推銷
I'm sick of this hand-to-mouth hustling.
你認為我不是
You think I'm not?
-我得走了 夥計 去
-I got to go, man. -Go?
-我們是搭檔 夥計 任何…合作夥伴
-We're partners, man. Any... -Partners?
夥計 我承擔風險
Man, I take the risk.
我今天看到有人被帶走了
I saw someone get taken today.
是的 好吧 我在外面忙著 結束交易
Yeah, well, I'm out here hustling, closing the deals,
當你在嬰兒床上的時候 只是在踢背 冷 嗯
while you're at the crib just kicking back, chilling, huh?
聽著 我得照顧好自己和魯拉
Look, I got to take care of myself and Rula.
你和Rula
You and Rula?
好吧 夥計 很好
All right, man, fine.
準備好你的側片 我要單獨去
Have your side piece. I'll go solo.
我不是在和你玩 尤吉斯
I'm not playing with you, Jurgis.
嘿 快點 寒冷 寒冷 喲 我不是…
-Hey, come on. Chill, chill. -Yo, I'm not...
嘿 嘿 嘿 冷靜 喲
Hey. hey, hey, chill, yo.
倒霉
Shit!
上車
Get in the car.
特別部門沒什麼好做的
Special Branch ain't got nothing better to do?
來自當地
From your local.
你想要什麼
What do you want?
你對鳳凰城瞭解多少
What do you know about Phoenix?
I'm not one of your narcs.
我不是你的毒品
What are you doing down here, Gabriel?
你在這裏幹什麼 加布裏埃爾
You're lucky to have your job.
你很幸運有你的工作
I didn't ask you for it.
我沒有問你
I don't want you winding up like your brother.
我不希望你像你哥哥那樣結束
-You mean dead? -I mean on the wrong side.
-你是說死了 -我是說站錯了方向
It runs in the family.
它在家庭中運行
You have no right to be talking about my family.
你無權談論我的家人
Your dad was my partner.
你爸爸是我的搭檔
I have a responsibility to that.
我對此負有責任
You have a choice to make yourself.
你有自己的選擇
Don't make the wrong one.
別弄錯了
Get out of here.
離開這裏
You got my money?
你有我的錢嗎
Hey, let's do this. I got the cigarette.
嘿 我們開始吧 我拿到煙了
Hey, hey, hey. You said to bring it here.
嘿 嘿 嘿 你說把它拿過來
Get in.
當選
Yo, I'm just trying to get paid, man.
嘿 我只是想得到報酬 夥計
-No, I'm not getting in, no. -Come on.
-不 我不進去 不-來吧
Hey, hey, hey.
嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey, yo, look, man.
嘿 喲 看 夥計
Man, you came to me, remember?
夥計 你來找我了 記得嗎
-Put this on. -Yo, what is this?
-把這個放在 -喲 這是什麼
Yo, what is this?
喲 這是什麼
Wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
等待 等等 等等 等等 等等 等等
Yo. No one said nothing about going nowhere.
喲 沒有人說什麼也不去
Get out.
走出
Follow me.
跟著我
Let's go.
走吧
Wicker Park.
柳條公園
What are we doing here?
我們在這裏做什麼
You want to get paid, don't you?
你想得到報酬 是嗎
That jacket's still too big for you.
那件夾克對你來說還是太大了
Baby brother.
小弟弟
What happened?
怎麼搞的
Before we could get the roaches, they got us.
我們還沒來得及弄到蟑螂 他們就把我們弄到手了
I'm the only one that made it out.
我是唯一一個成功的人
Wait, your...
等等 你的…
Your bug...
你的錯誤…
-Where's it at? -Gone.
-在哪裏 -走了
-No, that's impossible. -A few of us are off the grid now.
-不 那是不可能的 -我們中的一些人現在脫離了網絡
-Few of who? -I don't know the others.
-誰很少 -我不認識其他人
The others don't know me. It's better that way.
其他人不認識我 這樣更好
I don't exist anymore.
我不再存在了
In some ways, I am dead.
在某些方面 我已經死了
You couldn't come find me?
你找不到我
I wanted to, but there's narcs everywhere. You know that. Even in Pilsen.
我想去 但到處都是毒品 你知道的 即使在Pilsen
The Drummond brothers are back.
德拉蒙德兄弟回來了
For good. I'm dialed in, Rafe.
永遠好 我接通了 雷夫
My friend, he lives by the lakeshore. He has this boat.
我的朋友 他住在湖邊 他有這艘船
-We have this plan and... -G.
-我們有這個計劃…
-...we're gonna go across the lake... -G.
-…我們要穿過湖…
This... is the plan.
這個…就是這個計劃
I knew you'd get it.
我知道你會明白的
So, what'd I get you?
那麼 我給你買了什麼
Information.
信息
Information for who?
誰的信息
Only Number One knows.
只有頭號人才知道
-Number One? -Mm-hmm.
一號
Who the hell is that?
那到底是誰
No one knows. It's like I told you.
沒有人知道 就像我告訴你的
It's better that way.
這樣更好
Bad times coming.
糟糕的時刻即將來臨
Here. This will help you get out.
在這裏 這將幫助你擺脫困境
Go to the lake house.
去湖邊小屋
Not next week, not tomorrow. Now.
不是下周 不是明天 現在
-Before it get dark. -Come with me.
-在天黑之前 -跟我來
Not again, Rafe. Not again!
又不是了 雷夫 不要再這樣
We just got to take care of ourselves.
我們得照顧好自己
What'd Dad say the day we tried to get out?
我們想出去的那天爸爸怎麼說
Regroup. Fight back.
重新組合 反擊
-And he dead now. -Watch your mouth.
-他現在死了 -注意你的嘴
Let the roaches come and take what they want if they want it so bad.
讓蟑螂來拿走他們想要的東西 如果他們這麼想的話
And we can start all over, Rafe.
我們可以從頭再來 雷夫
We can get back to the way that things used to be.
我們可以回到過去的樣子
Don't you get it?
你不明白嗎
Harmony, peace, unity... it's all bullshit.
和諧 和平 團結……全是胡說八道
It's a lie, Gabe. They gonna take everything.
這是個謊言 加布 他們會拿走一切
In a few years, they'll have stripped us to nothing.
再過幾年 他們就會把我們剝得一文不值
Got one more chance to light a fire big enough so the whole world can see.
再給我一次機會點燃足夠大的火 讓全世界都能看到
To prove to everybody out there that the roaches can be beat.
向在場的所有人證明蟑螂是可以被打敗的
Light a match.
點燃火柴
Ignite a war.
點燃一場戰爭
Long as we fight back, we got a chance.
只要我們反擊 我們就有機會
Why you always got to be the hero?
為什麼你總是要成為英雄
You got to pick a side.
你得選一邊
You got to pick a side, Gabe. One day, you have to, or this is it.
加布 你得選一邊 總有一天 你必須 否則就是這樣
You got to go.
你得走了
Gabe, when this is all over,
蓋布 當這一切結束的時候
I'll find you.
我會找到你的
I promise.
我保證
You just got to go.
你得走了
Now.
現在
Got him.
抓住他了
Baby, what's going on?
寶貝 怎麼了
We're getting out.
我們要出去了
Okay.
可以
Well, before we do that, why don't we just...
好吧 在我們這麼做之前 我們為什麼不…
Grab this. And take only what you can carry.
抓住這個 只帶你能帶的東西
What did you do?
你做了什麼
There's gonna be some trouble.
會有麻煩的
Gabriel, what is that supposed to mean?
加布裏埃爾 這是什麼意思
What, come on, you're freaking me out.
什麼 拜託 你把我嚇壞了
Rafe...
Rafe…
is alive.
是活著的
Your brother?
你哥哥
Yeah.
是啊
Nice try, Gabriel.
很好 加布裏埃爾
What did he say? Where did you see him?
他說了什麼 你在哪裏見到他的
That's about enough to last us a couple weeks.
這就足夠我們維持幾個星期了
After that, we're gonna have to make it on our own.
在那之後 我們必須自己去做
No, we won't make it past the first checkpoint.
不 我們不能通過第一個檢查站
Not if we go across the lake.
如果我們過湖就不行了
I've got a boat that we can use.
我有一條船可以用
There's nothing over there. There's no law. It's dangerous.
那邊什麼都沒有 包括法律 很危險
You're not listening to me.
你沒聽我說
They're planning something.
他們在計劃什麼
Okay, and if we go, we are involved. No way.
好吧 如果我們走了 我們就參與進來了 沒辦法
-Baby, baby. Come on. -No.
-寶貝 寶貝 來吧 -沒有
Gabriel, if you want to keep me safe, you need to stay.
加布裏埃爾 如果你想保護我的安全 你需要留下來
Please.
拜託
-No, I can't. -No, Gabriel.
-不 我不能-不 加布裏埃爾
-I can't, I can't. -Gabriel, this is crazy.
-我不能 我不能-加布裏埃爾 這太瘋狂了
Please, let's talk about this!
拜託 我們談談這個
Type this. Send it to PDHQ. Fast.
鍵入此 發送到PDHQ 快
Move!
移動
-Can they track us? -No. I got a few mirror IPs.
-他們能追蹤我們嗎 -不 我有一些鏡像IP
Got him. There's your target.
抓住他了 這是你的目標
Consider yourself as informed as Special Branch.
把你自己當作特別的分支機構
So, who is he?
那麼 他是誰
Just another collaborator. Mayor's deputy.
只是另一個合作者 市長的副手
No, no.
不 不
Who is he?
他是誰
He carries the bomb.
他帶著炸彈
-Classifieds. -Got room for one more?
分類廣告 -還有空間再放一個嗎
One more.
再一個
The late edition?
最新版本
They proofread the scratch till 3:30.
他們把劃痕校對到3:30
Real important, Rittenhouse.
真的很重要 麗頓豪斯
Yeah. Thank you.
是啊 謝謝您
This is a request going out.
這是一個請求
Hi.
你好
Who wants to go first?
誰想先去
Get him off the table.
把他從桌子上拿下來
Next. Hurry.
下一步 快點
Get her in here.
把她帶進來
His heart rate went below the limit and distressed his bug.
他的心率低於極限 使他的蟲子很難受
Drones are maternal to all bugs. We have to get yours out now.
無人機是所有昆蟲的母體 我們現在得把你的拿出來
Got it.
知道了
Don't move. I'll stitch you up.
別動 我給你縫針
All right.
好的
These three bugs are the three insiders. Heart attack, cancer, unlucky car wreck.
這三個蟲子是三個內部人 心臟病發作 癌癥 不幸的車禍
Downtown folks, spotless records.
市中心的人們 一塵不染的記錄
The other three are good enough for your drivers.
另外三個對你的司機來說足夠好了
I need two now.
我現在需要兩個
All right, my shift ends at 7:00 a.m. tomorrow.
好吧 我的班明天早上7點結束
That's the latest I can log them in as deceased.
這是最新的我可以將他們作為死者登錄的
That's as long as they're good for. They get ID'd after that, they're it.
只要他們能勝任就行 在那之後他們會得到身份證 他們就是
You're gonna need these plates to keep the bugs down in their mouth.
你需要這些盤子把蟲子放在嘴裏
Semper fi, Sergeant.
Semper FI 中士
I always did believe in life after death.
我一直相信死後的生活
Is that you, Father?
是你嗎 爸爸
Come on back.
回來吧
What you got me?
你抓了我什麼
The last of it.
最後一個
Wait here.
在這兒等著
Now, I assume I don't have to tell you what they'll do
現在 我想我不必告訴你他們會怎麼做
if they find this on your person.
如果他們在你的人身上發現這個
Where'd you get this?
你從哪兒弄來的
Their ship crashed, too.
他們的船也墜毀了
Attaches best to natural fiber, human hair, cotton or wool,
最好與天然纖維 人發 棉花或羊毛搭配
but because it's not chemically based, it's undetectable to scanners.
但因為它不是化學成分 所以掃瞄儀無法檢測到
Because it's organic, it passes through all security.
因為它是有機的 它通過所有的安全
You can smuggle this in anywhere.
你可以把這個偷運到任何地方
And when you arm it, it's a chameleon.
當你武裝它的時候 它是變色龍
How do we arm it?
我們如何武裝它
Double tap gives you about 60 seconds.
雙擊會給你60秒
Drivers are downstairs.
司機在樓下
Holy hell.
神聖地獄
Take that off.
把它拿下來
You may as well be wearing a target.
你還不如穿上靶子
All right, these implants get logged as deceased at 7:00 a.m. tomorrow.
好吧 這些植入物明天早上7點被記錄為死亡
After that, you're dead to the world.
在那之後 你就死定了
You know what happens to Pilsen if they correctly ID us.
你知道如果皮爾森能正確識別我們的身份 他們會怎麼樣
Any contact, before and after, with any friends or family
與任何朋友或家人在之前和之後的任何接觸
puts the entire operation at risk.
使整個行動處於危險之中
Remember...
記得
he gets us to them.
他讓我們找到他們
No one gets taken alive.
沒有人被活捉
Okay.
可以
You ready? Here we go.
準備好了嗎 我們走吧
Courage.
勇氣
-Make a right out of here. -I got it.
-從這裏右轉 -我明白了
People of Chicago...
芝加哥人…
welcome to a special night of coming together,
歡迎來到特別的聚會之夜
of sharing.
分享
And tonight, we have some very special guests joining us.
今晚 我們有一些非常特別的客人加入我們
Before first contact, our political system was broken.
在第一次接觸之前 我們的政治制度被打破了
We were fighting among ourselves in the halls of Congress
我們在國會大廳裏自相殘殺
and on the streets of this great city,
在這座大城市的街道上
slowly bleeding to death.
慢慢流血至死
And we needed change.
我們需要改變
We needed someone to show us a better way.
我們需要有人給我們一個更好的方法
Well, the facts speak for themselves.
好吧 事實本身就說明了問題
Natural resource production has increased tenfold.
自然資源產量增加了十倍
Employment is at record levels. Crime at an all-time low.
就業率達到創紀錄水平 犯罪率創歷史新低
Pays to play the game.
玩這個遊戲是值得的
And we have the Legislators to thank
我們要感謝立法者
for this American renaissance!
為了美國的復興
So, will you please join me in giving them a real hometown welcome
所以 你能和我一起給他們一個真正的家鄉的歡迎嗎
that truly shows our appreciation
這真的表達了我們的謝意
for nine years of peace and prosperity!
九年的和平與繁榮
Mary Johnson, 8:39 p.m.
瑪麗約翰遜 晚上8:39
Window down, sir.
車窗朝下 先生
Enjoy the show tonight, sir.
先生 請欣賞今晚的演出
[crowd continues cheering
人群繼續歡呼
I'm inside.
我在裏面
"E" section.
E 部分
Ladies and gentlemen, the United State of America.
女士們先生們 美利堅合眾國
What a performance, ladies and gentlemen.
女士們先生們 表演得真好
A colorful reenactment of nine years ago.
九年前的多彩重現
They're running this thing like clockwork. We got to give it to 'em.
他們像鐘錶一樣運轉著 我們得把它給他們
He's leaving the VIP section now.
他現在要離開貴賓區
What a privilege it is...
這是多麼的榮幸…
Can you see him?
你能看見他嗎
I see him. He's on the field. We're in position.
我看見他了 他在球場上 我們就位了
He's not coming to
他不會來的
He's going the other way, towards the tunnel behind you.
他走另一條路 朝你身後的隧道走去
Got it.
知道了
Ladies and gentlemen, please rise to greet our Legislature.
女士們先生們 請起立迎接我們的立法機關
He's coming right at you.
他馬上就來找你
Robert Watts?
羅伯特·沃茨
It's Ben. Ben Simon. Drexel Drive.
是本 本·西蒙 德雷克塞爾驅動器
Keep it moving.
保持移動
Sorry about it. Sorry about it.
對不起 很抱歉
Hands off of me.
放開我
Allow me time to translate.
請給我時間翻譯
Breathe between sentences.
在句子之間呼吸
We need to allow them to communicate first.
我們需要讓他們先溝通
...this is Zero-4 citywide dispatch. Heavy smoke.
…這是全城的零-4派遣 濃煙
We got half in zone security unit...
我們有一半在區域安全部門…
...unaccounted for, possible Legislator.
…不明原因 可能的立法者
Come on.
來吧
Don't move!
別動
Get in the car! Get in!
上車 當選
Keep them out there!
把它們放在外面
Keep that crowd back! You are hereby ordered...
把人群往後退 特此命令…
Come on! We got to go!
加油 我們得走了
Oh, no.
哦 不
Oh, fuck.
哦 他媽的
You and me go together.
你和我一起去
We got till 7:00 a.m.
我們一直到早上7點
What people need to understand is this is a war.
人們需要理解的是 這是一場戰爭
Between order and chaos.
在秩序和混亂之間
Between democracy and anarchy.
在民主和無政府狀態之間
Commissioner Igoe, is the insurgency reorganizing?
伊戈專員 叛亂正在重組嗎
"Insurgency." No one's mentioned that word since Wicker Park.
叛亂  自從威克公園以來 沒有人提到過這個詞
There are rumors that hunters are being brought in.
有傳言說獵人被帶進來了
Measures are being taken, but to preserve their effectiveness,
正在採取措施 但為了保持有效性
I'm not gonna discuss them.
我不想討論他們
And we will keep you updated as the situation evolves.
隨著形勢的發展 我們會不斷更新您的信息
-No, a question over here. -Thank you.
-不 這裏有個問題 謝謝
Commander. Commissioner Igoe is ready for you.
指揮官 伊戈專員準備好了
They're bringing in hunters this time from off planet.
這次他們從地球外引進了獵人
-They can't do that. -The one ID we have,
-他們不能那樣做 -我們有一個身份證
the ex-priest from Saint Anthony's, points to Pilsen.
聖安東尼的前牧師指向皮爾森
You know what that means.
你知道那意味著什麼
We can clean this up ourselves.
我們可以自己清理
Yeah, nobody's talking about a cleanup.
是的 沒人在說清理
Pilsen isn't Wicker Park, Commissioner.
皮爾森不是威克公園 局長
Yeah, not yet.
是的 還沒有
They torch this neighborhood,
他們在這附近放火
the network will go to ground just like they did last time.
網絡會像上次一樣接地
You know, you're too sentimental, Bill. Pilsen's a goddamn armpit.
你知道嗎 比爾 你太多愁善感了 皮爾森是個該死的腋窩
Only good for whoring.
只適合嫖娼
Their leadership is in Pilsen.
他們的領導是在皮爾森
-You know that for a fact? -I'm working on it.
-你知道嗎 -我正在努力
Not fast enough.
速度不夠快
If we do our job, we can locate the end of the thread, their Number One,
如果我們做我們的工作 我們可以找到線程的末端 它們的第一個
and unravel the whole network.
解開整個網絡
Look, let me stop you right there.
聽著 讓我在那兒攔住你
Hey, that ship has sailed.
嘿 那艘船已經開航了
And I have to explain why to them in there.
我必須向他們解釋為什麼在那裏
I got a positive ID at Soldier Field, the man I've been tracking for two years.
我在士兵場找到了一個身份證 那是我追蹤了兩年的人
I need time to bring him in alive.
我需要時間讓他活著進來
You're not listening.
你沒在聽
Right now, we have resources behind us.
現在 我們有了資源
Now, you might not see them, but they're there. They're protecting you.
現在 你可能看不到他們 但他們在那裏 他們在保護你
And the more irrational you become, the more unnecessary noise you make,
你變得越不理智 發出的噪音就越不必要
the harder it's gonna be to invite you into the lifeboat.
邀請你上救生艇就越難了
Do you understand me?
你明白我的意思嗎
If there's any chance of getting off this dying rock,
如果有機會從這片垂死的岩石上下來
I'm not gonna waste it.
我不會浪費它的
Pilsen is already dead.
皮爾森已經死了
They just don't know it yet.
他們只是還不知道
They hate the way we smell.
他們討厭我們的氣味
How about that?
那怎麼樣
Sorry I got to leave you here, Bill. Can't take anybody with me.
對不起 我得把你留在這裏 比爾 不能帶任何人和我在一起
If you only knew what was inside this place.
如果你只知道這裏面是什麼
The commissioner's privilege, sir.
局長的特權 先生
You know it.
你知道的
And don't get hung up on this, Bill. Play ball.
別掛斷電話 比爾 玩球
And keep your hands clean. Let the hunters do the dirty work.
保持雙手清潔 讓獵人干髒活
And I'll tell our friends down below they got our full operational support.
我會告訴下面的朋友 他們得到了我們的全面運營支持
Now, go home, relax, take the night off for once, huh?
現在 回家 放鬆 休息一次 嗯
All the second-stage tanks now pressurized.
所有的二級坦克現在都加壓了
Thirty-five seconds and counting.
35秒後開始計數
We are still go. Thirty seconds and counting.
我們還在走 三十秒後開始計數
Feels good. T-minus 25 now.
感覺很好 現在減去25
Let's ride this one out, Bill.
比爾 讓我們騎這個出去
Confirming rank and identity.
確認等級和身份
Commissioner Eugene Igoe.
尤金·伊戈委員
Let them take the lead. Just until it dies down.
讓他們帶頭 直到它消失
Security clearance complete.
安全許可完成
-Ten, nine... -Prepare for descent.
-十 九…-準備降落
Ignition sequence start.
點火順序啟動
Six, five, four, three, two, one.
六 五 四 三 二 一
I can't protect you now.
我現在不能保護你
I know.
我知道
I have faith in you.
我對你有信心
Why?
為什麼
Why do you? Nobody else does.
你為什麼 其他人都沒有
We could go away together.
我們可以一起走
That's not our story.
這不是我們的故事
Dance with me.
和我一起跳舞
You have a job to do.
你有工作要做
Move, move, move! Let's go! Let's go!
快 快 快 走吧 走吧
Get back! Move back!
回來 往後退
Dad, Wake up!
爸爸 醒醒
You got to get moving now! You got to move back! Hurry up!
你得走了 你得後退 快點
Mom, wake up. Mom, wake up. Specials are here!
媽媽 醒醒 媽媽 醒醒 特色菜來了
Everyone, get on the ground now! Get down! Get down!
所有人 馬上趴在地上 趴下 趴下
Specials are here! Specials are here! Specials are here! Wake up!
有好東西  醒醒
That's it. Enough of this shit!
就是這樣 夠了
Move, move, move!
快 快 快
Don't turn your head. Face the wall!
別轉頭 面對牆
Specials! Specials are here!
特價商品 特色菜來了
Move now!
現在就行動
-Gabriel Drummond. -Get your hands on the wall.
-加布裏埃爾·德拉蒙德 -把手放在牆上
Do you know him? Have you seen him?
你認識他嗎 你見過他嗎
Rafael Drummond. Who knows him?
拉斐爾·德拉蒙德 誰認識他
-Hands on the wall. -Hey, look what we got here.
-把手放在牆上 -嘿 看這裏有什麼
Hey, where'd you get all this money, huh?
嘿 你從哪兒弄到這麼多錢的
What are you selling to get all that money? Carry a weapon?
你賣什麼來得到這些錢？ 攜帶武器
I asked you a question, punk.
我問你一個問題 朋克
Try that cowboy shit with me? Let's see where that goes, huh?
和我一起試試那個牛仔的狗屎 讓我們看看去哪兒 嗯
Are you kidding me?
你在開玩笑吧
Who the cowboy now, huh?
現在誰是牛仔
Huh?
嗯
What are you gonna do, Gabriel?
你要怎麼做 加布裏埃爾
Shoot him?
開槍打死他
Go ahead, shoot.
去吧 開槍
Kill the bastard. You know it'll make you feel better.
殺了那個混蛋 你知道這會讓你感覺更好
Come on, get rid of some of that rage.
快點 別再生氣了
-Take them all in. -Move, move, move!
-把他們都帶進去 -快 快 快
In this neighborhood, we shoot our own guys.
在這附近 我們射殺自己的人
Target one man, Rafael Drummond, moving on a fraudulent implant.
針對一名男子 拉斐爾·德魯蒙德 進行了假體植入
Hello?
你好
I'm sorry I couldn't say it before.
很抱歉我以前不能說
I'm doing this for Charlie.
我是為查理做的
There's someone here who wants to talk to you.
這裏有人想和你談談
Hello, Evan. Tell us where your friends are going.
你好 埃文 告訴我們你的朋友要去哪裏
This is a security message. If you see something, say something.
這是一條安全信息 如果你看到什麼 說點什麼
Ladies and gentlemen,
女士們先生們
last call for boarding for buses heading to New York City and Montreal,
最後一個去紐約和蒙特利爾的巴士上車的電話
departure set for 7:00.
出發時間為7:00
All units, stand down. Requisite hunter units traveling.
所有單位 站住 必要的狩獵單位旅行
I don't want to go in.
我不想進去
Last call for boarding
最後一次登機
for buses heading to New York City and Montreal.
去紐約和蒙特利爾的巴士
Just push the door and come through.
只要把門推開就行了
I don't want to go in.
我不想進去
You're making us late, Charlie. Would you just push the door.
你讓我們遲到了 查理 你能把門推一下嗎
Fine.
好的
Thank you. Thank you very much.
謝謝您 非常感謝
On the ground now!
現在就趴在地上
Hands behind your head!
雙手放在腦後
Sit down! Sit down!
坐下來 坐下來
Hey!
嘿
You! Get down now! I said down!
你 馬上下來 我說了下去
It's not over.
還沒有結束
Somebody kill me!
有人殺了我
I want a lawyer.
我想要個律師
In another ten...
再過十年…
nine and a half hours, there'll be nothing left of Pilsen.
九個半小時後 皮爾森就什麼都沒有了
I said I want a lawyer.
我說我想要個律師
You and I both know those days are gone.
你和我都知道那些日子已經過去了
I didn't need a warrant when I burned your boat.
我燒了你的船不需要搜查令
You work for me now, Gabriel.
你現在為我工作 加布裏埃爾
I told you...
我告訴過你…
I'm not one of your narcs.
我不是你的毒品
I'm not gonna do shit for you.
我不會為你做狗屎的
I'm not asking you to do anything for me.
我不是要你為我做任何事
I'm not even asking you to do anything for your community.
我甚至沒有要求你為你的社區做任何事
Even though plenty of people are going to die.
即使很多人都會死去
Like your father, you're more of a family guy.
像你父親一樣 你更像一個家庭成員
Blood first.
先血
When's the last time you saw your brother?
你最後一次見到你弟弟是什麼時候
I'm not gonna tell you shit.
我不會告訴你的
So you can do whatever you want to do to me.
所以你想對我做什麼就做什麼
You got a visitor.
你有個訪客
Family day.
家庭日
You want to say something?
你想說點什麼
Go ahead. He can hear you.
前進 他能聽見你說話
Baby brother, why...
弟弟 為什麼…
Why didn't you listen?
你為什麼不聽
What you doing here, man?
你在這裏幹什麼 夥計
No.
不
No! No! Gabe! Hey, don't!
不 不 加布 嘿 別這樣
Don't let 'em use you! You hear me? You hear me?
別讓他們利用你 你聽見了嗎 你聽見了嗎
Man, I told you not... I told you not to be a hero, Rafe.
夥計 我告訴過你不要…我告訴過你不要做英雄 雷夫
-Don't do it! -I told you not to be the hero!
-別這麼做 -我告訴過你不要做英雄
Look, don't do it, Gabe.
聽著 別這樣 加布
I told you, I'm already dead, man.
我告訴過你 我已經死了 夥計
Do it, and I'll make sure he lives.
去做吧 我會確保他活著的
You expect me to trust you?
你希望我相信你
Gabe, you there? Gabe?
加布 你在嗎 加布
Fuck!
艸
Listen to me carefully, Gabriel.
仔細聽我說 加布裏埃爾
Right now, the Legislators are preparing to level Pilsen
現在 立法者正準備將皮爾森調平
for what your brother's done.
因為你哥哥的所作所為
Same way they leveled Wicker Park.
他們用同樣的方法平整了柳條公園
Our roundups are over.
我們的總結結束了
You are our one way into the network.
你是我們進入網絡的唯一途徑
I need you to deliver a message from the Phoenix.
我需要你從鳳凰城傳遞信息
You will not ask questions.
你不會問問題的
Do exactly what I say, and your brother will live.
照我說的做 你哥哥就活了
Understand?
明白了嗎
When you wanted to deliver something before, where did you go?
當你以前想送東西的時候 你去哪裏了
Give them this.
把它們給他們
Is that Gabe?
那是加布嗎
What are you doing here?
你在這裏幹什麼
I got a message from the Phoenix.
我收到鳳凰社的消息
He's inside the van.
他在車裏
Come on, man, move, move!
快點 夥計 快點 快點
The door's open.
門開了
Show him what you showed me.
給他看你給我看的
Don't, don't, don't. Don't.
不要 不要 不要 不要
I'm Rafe's brother.
我是雷夫的哥哥
Put it down.
把它放下
There's no Rafe here.
這裏沒有雷夫
What do you want?
你想要什麼
How'd you know about this?
你怎麼知道的
Make the call.
打電話
Subject moving west.
物體向西移動
-Now, boss? -Not yet.
-現在 老闆 -還沒有
You should've left already.
你應該已經走了
No, our orders are to stay until the end.
不 我們的命令要一直到最後
I think this is the end.
我想這就是結局
They got him at the bus station.
他們在公共汽車站抓住了他
What if we got it wrong?
如果我們弄錯了怎麼辦
He's asking to be taken to Number One.
他要求被帶到第一位
Says he knows a way into the Closed Zone.
他說他知道進入封閉區的方法
Gabriel?
加布裏埃爾
You know him?
你認識他嗎
He was a student of mine.
他是我的學生
So, what do we do now?
那麼 我們現在該怎麼辦
Deliver the message to Number One.
把信息傳遞給第一位
Subject moving north.
主題向北移動
Subject traveling.
主題旅行
All units, remain out of sight.
所有單位 保持在視線之外
It's the Pilsen brothel.
是皮爾森妓院
Follow her upstairs.
跟著她上樓
Now we go.
現在我們走
-All right! -Move, move, move!
-好吧 -快 快 快
Hello, Gabriel.
你好 加布裏埃爾
How...
怎樣
how do you know my name?
你怎麼知道我的名字
Now.
現在
-Down! Come on! Don't move! -Gun!
-下來 加油 別動 槍
Stand down until I arrive.
站下來 直到我到達
You know this place?
你知道這個地方嗎
No.
不
Hooker is a history buff.
胡克是個歷史迷
Clip's empty. I don't get it.
剪輯是空的 我不明白
Huh.
呵呵
Only picture on the wall.
只有牆上的照片
This us?
這是我們嗎
It's her own setup.
這是她自己的安排
Communication line to the Closed Zone is now open.
到封閉區域的通信線路現在打開
Name, rank, department.
姓名 級別 部門
Mulligan, William.
威廉·穆裏根
Commander. Pilsen Special Branch.
指揮官 皮爾森特別分行
Let's begin the debrief. Proceed.
讓我們開始匯報吧 繼續進行
The computer we found contained all names, aliases and locations
我們找到的計算機包含所有名稱 別名和位置
of the Chicago network.
芝加哥網絡
This communication sent some years before restrictions.
這封信比限制條件早了幾年
Proof of a national network.
國家網絡的證明
The computer belonged to the prostitute?
電腦中那個是妓女嗎
Number One.
第一
She recorded her interactions with her johns
她錄下了她和約翰的互動
and sent relevant information out through the network's chain.
並通過網絡鏈發送相關信息
Her second in command was Charles Rittenhouse, communications,
她的副手是通訊部的查爾斯·裏滕豪斯
responsible for activating the operation known as Phoenix.
負責激活被稱為鳳凰城的行動
Go. Get in.
去吧 當選
Number three, Patrick Ellison, operations.
第三 帕特裏克埃利森 運營部
-Before demobilization... -Wait here.
-退場前…-在這裏等著
...Marine Corps, ordnance.
…海軍陸戰隊 軍械
Wait, wait. No. I'm staying with you. I'm staying with you!
等等 等等 不 我和你住在一起 我要和你在一起
Number four, Raul Casillas, materials and transport.
第四 勞爾·卡西利亞斯 材料和運輸
Foreman at the Pilsen Auto Yards.
皮爾森汽車廠的工頭
Systems analyst Ivan Leviev
系統分析師伊凡列維耶夫
hacked into our central surveillance database
侵入我們的中央監控數據庫
and tracked Deputy Mayor Robert Watts, the unwitting courier of the bomb.
並追蹤了副市長羅伯特·沃茨 他是炸彈的情報員
Harrison Ma, a medical student before the closures,
關閉前的醫科學生 哈里森馬
developed a procedure to remove identity implants,
開發了移除身份植入物的程序
enabling the cell to remain invisible to tracker drones.
使手機對無人機保持隱形
These were the principals hiding in plain sight
這些是隱藏在眼前的主要人物
who enabled the cell to carry out the attack on Soldier Field.
是誰讓這個小分隊在戰場上發動攻擊的
The search for militant suspects has accelerated.
對武裝分子嫌疑犯的搜查已經加速
An unidentified female resident is reported to have been shot and killed.
據報道 一名身份不明的女性居民被槍殺
But once we had their Number One,
但一旦我們有了他們的頭號
they knew we had them, too.
他們知道我們也有
The Chicago network...
芝加哥網絡…
is neutralized.
被中和
What was her name and background?
她的名字和背景是什麼
Her name was Priscilla Scott.
她的名字叫普裏西拉·斯科特
She was a history teacher at Pilsen Elementary.
她是皮爾森小學的歷史老師
She was off the grid for nine years, so there's nothing else we know about her.
她已經九年沒有上網了 所以我們對她一無所知
A prostitute. Why?
妓女為什麼
Access.
訪問
She groomed her clients very carefully, procured members of the Unity government,
她非常仔細地為客戶服務 為團結政府的成員提供服務
and manipulated them into divulging classified information,
操縱他們洩露機密信息
which she recorded with her concealed wire.
她用隱藏的電線記錄下來的
Play the tape, please.
請放錄音帶
Can you imagine what they do down there?
你能想像他們在下面做什麼嗎
Stripping everything.
剝去一切
Every crevasse. Fracking to the power often.
每個裂縫 經常水力壓裂
Taking it all off planet.
把一切都從地球上帶走
You felt those earthquakes.
你感覺到了地震
They'll crawl. They stand.
他們會匍匐前進 他們站著
It's all the same to them.
對他們來說都一樣
They have this network of tunnels under the surface...
他們有地下隧道網…
Wait. You've been inside the Closed Zone?
等待 你在禁區內
No, not me. The commissioner.
不 不是我 專員
He's the guy with the access.
他就是那個有權進入的人
Well, then we better get business out of the way.
好吧 那我們最好把生意讓開
Yeah, it's a big deal.
是的 這是一件大事
How often do they come out of the Closed Zone?
他們多久從封閉區出來一次
Robert Watts, he's just this alderman's bagman,
羅伯特·沃茨 他就是這位議員的推銷員
but he'll be handling them out at the rally.
但他會在集會上處理他們
Greeting them, taking them in.
問候他們 帶他們進來
That's an incredible responsibility.
這是一項不可思議的責任
Mm-hmm. What if I told you that the roach governor may be one of them?
嗯 如果我告訴你蟑螂總督可能是他們中的一員呢
-Oh... -Stop the tape, please.
-哦…-請停止錄音
Eugene.
尤金
Our own chain of command was compromised.
我們自己的指揮鏈被破壞了
What about you?
那你呢
What about me?
我呢
You live in this neighborhood.
你住在這附近
Yes.
對
These are your people.
這些是你的人
Evidence will be analyzed by the Legislature.
立法機構將分析證據
In the meantime, as acting commissioner,
同時 作為代理專員
you are to report to the Closed Zone for further orders.
你要向封閉區報到以獲得進一步的訂單
No more questions.
別再問了
Loading up!
裝貨
Lines in a single file.
單個文件中的行
Rafe's alive.
雷夫還活著
Yeah, so what?
是啊 那又怎麼樣
I don't mean nothing to him anymore.
我對他不再意味著什麼了
-You had a purpose. -There was no purpose.
-你有一個目標 -沒有目的
Rafe's plan failed.
雷夫的計劃失敗了
What if the plan was to fail?
如果計劃失敗怎麼辦
Like I said, you work for me now.
就像我說的 你現在為我工作
And what do you want me to do with this?
你想讓我怎麼辦
Did you pay attention in history class, Gabriel?
加布裏埃爾 你在歷史課上注意過嗎
Beware of Greeks bearing gifts.
提防帶禮物的希臘人
Now, get out.
現在 滾出去
Commissioner Mulligan. They made you the big man, Bill.
穆裏根委員 他們讓你成為大人物 比爾
Look out for us when you get down there, Commissioner.
你下來的時候要當心我們 局長
Here we are.
我們到了
Oh, Lord. Johnny, no. Well, I'm all sweaty.
哦 上帝 約翰尼 不 嗯 我都出汗了
-Come on, baby, you look beautiful. -No...
-來吧 寶貝 你看起來很漂亮 -不…
-Priss, Charles! -Hi!
-普裏斯 查爾斯 -嗨
Words of advice from a history teacher
歷史老師的忠告
to the future generation?
給下一代
Hi, baby Gabriel. I can't wait to cuddle you.
嗨 寶貝加布裏埃爾 我等不及要擁抱你了
That's not advice.
這不是建議
Bill, how about you?
比爾 你呢
I'm off duty, John. You got a problem, call 911.
約翰 我下班了 你有問題 打911
Get up here. You know Priss.
站起來 你知道Priss
She teaches at the school with my wife.
她和我妻子在學校教書
-Hi. How are you? -Priss.
-嗨 你好嗎 -普裏斯
Bill, any advice?
比爾 有什麼建議嗎
Oh, yeah.
哦 是的
Teacher or cop, kid? You got to make a choice.
老師還是警察 孩子 你必須做出選擇
Whatever you are, be a good one.
無論你是誰 都要做一個好人
You got a hell of a family here, kid.
孩子 你家真是太好了
-Thank you. -And not just them. All of us.
謝謝 -不僅僅是他們 我們所有人
Pilsen's got you covered.
皮爾森掩護了你
The future is yours, kid.
未來是你的 孩子
Confirming rank and identity.
確認等級和身份
Commissioner William Mulligan.
威廉·穆裏根委員
Security clearance complete.
安全許可完成
Prepare for descent.
準備降落
Fifteen seconds. Guidance is internal.
15秒 指導是內部的
12, 11, ten, nine...
12 11 10 9…
Ignition sequence start.
點火順序啟動
Six, five, four, three, two, one.
六 五 四 三 二 一
Drop.
掉下來
Light a match.
點燃火柴
Ignite a war.
點燃一場戰爭
Long as we fight back, we got a chance.
只要我們反擊 我們就有機會